

### **JENNY ADAMS**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### Profile

A hard-working front-end developer, equipped with industry standard languages, experience from two of Wellington's top web agencies, and a passion for positive change.

- Contact
- iennyadamsnz@gmail.com
- **2** 027 556 9938
- 亩 linkedin.com/in/jennyadamsnz
- jennyadamsnz.github.ic
- (interests
- Reading
- ♣ Travelling
- X DIY
- : New Technologies



#### **Employment**

NOV 2017 - PRESENT

#### Heyday

#### Front-End Developer

Building and maintaining commerical websites of notable brands built on SilverStripe. I did most of the Front-End work for barnardosearlylearning.org.nz and regularly maintain wellingtonzoo.com, drive.govt.nz, summerset.co.nz, powershop.co.nz, whittakers.co.nz, bankomb.org.nz, protectivesecurity.govt.nz, garageproject.co.nz & mmnz.co.nz

MAY 2017 - NOV 2017

#### Springload

#### Junior Front-End Developer

A fixed-term contract, primarily to maintain Kiwibank's legacy website while it was replaced. I also created email templates & helped create a pattern library for Xero's staff intranet.

AUG 2016 - MAY 2017Advice Unlimited

#### Web Development & Design

Working as part of a small team to build quick and affordable websites for small to medium sized businesses using Squarespace.



#### Education

MAY 2016 - MAY 2017

## Yoobee School of Design Diploma of Web Development

An introdutory course to front-end and back-end coding using HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Laravel, Wordpress.

**AUG** 2016 - MAY 2017

# Victoria University of Wellington Bachelor of Arts

Majoring in International Relations & Media Studies



#### Skills

LANGUAGES HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, JS,

PHP, Python, Django

**VERSION CONTROL** Git, Node.js, Gulp & TOOLS

SOFTWARE Invision, Sketch, Photoshop,

Zeplin, Jira, Harvest, Campaign

Monitor, Vagrant, Docker

CMSs SilverStripe, Laravel, Wordpress,

Wagtail, Squarespace